[Music]
mum mum hey mum look look they can I buy
this I already said we are just looking
around
put that back and quit bothering me but
mama it's the super limited edition
action figure I need it to complete my
collection limited edition how much does
it cost it's only $7 please I'll be the
coolest kid on a playground Call of Duty
isn't that the game you [ __ ] have
been playing all weekend damn it I told
Uncle Chuck not to let you rent those M
rated games and he lets you do it anyway
what do you need an action figure for
are you gonna stick it up your butt
that's none of your business
look at the cool gun toys it comes with
and the cool camo patterns on the box to
top it off it's a Walmart exclusive this
may be our one and only chance Call of
Duty is the best you get to shoot people
and stuff me and medic always play bla
bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla
bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla I'm not
buying this [ __ ] go put it back where
you got it I ain't got seven dollars to
waste on a piece of plastic that you
will just lose soon as we get home it
will be okay ro you can try asking for a
toy again next year mom never lets us
buy anything
mom can I get this $400 Barbie
Dreamhouse set um Sonia don't you
already have six of those things back
home what do you need more for uncle
Chuck got drunk and took a hammer to it
yesterday
don't you remember Oh IRA man ow but
Sonia surely you know we don't have the
money to I don't care I want it Sonic
Manic look what mom is going to buy for
me it's so cute you [ __ ]
look here it comes with two rooms
instead of one now Ken and Barbie can
have their own sex dungeon Lord forgive
me for what I would do to that 15
year-olds ass Charles go put back that
pack of fear today we can't afford both
that in the dream house what would you
say they called hit on 18 today Charles
don't make me count to three what he can
never have a anything missing yeah that
is family
[Music]
hey Sonic did you see that just now
I think somebody ran by us what are you
talking about I didn't see anything your
eyes need to get checked are you sure
door look there it goes again who or
what is that
go and catch it if you give a [ __ ] so
bad it's so fast I think it's a white
rabbit
how curious what is a rabbit doing
inside Walmart need to catch it and
release it outside before it hurts
itself somehow
ouch what happened where in the world
did I go off to
I was hoping for the fat one why are you
here
damn it now I'm late for a very
important date with my pal King eh
wait don't go I need you to tell me
where I am
darn he's already gone what am I going
to do now
I think I'll have a look around if I do
find someone maybe they can help me
[Music]
how the [ __ ] did I get here just what is
this place
they are those people over there maybe
if I ask nicely they could help me get
home thanks for coming to my own
birthday party man I can't believe
you're the only one who showed up I
invited like 50 people and they all said
they weren't coming because I'm too mad
I'm crazy I'm almost as crazy as Jared
littles Joker from the Suicide Squad
don't mention it Hatter it's your own
birthday
I don't care how crazy you are you are
still my best bud and [ __ ] haha thanks
for being a true [ __ ] now what do you
say we get this D time started oh yeah
you mad son of a [ __ ] you know how much
this bunny likes tea time is he drinking
tea out of his big smelly butt crack
this world is so strange
damn that's kind of hot though I wish I
was on the receiving end of that [ __ ]
Hatter stop look over there I think
somebody is watching us hey it's a girl
should we kill this [ __ ] I'm sorry I
didn't mean to eavesdrop I just got lost
in this forest and stopped by to ask you
guys for directions so please please
don't kill me of course if you want to
kill me I'd like to see you try I can't
exactly say it will end well for you
[Music]
so this place is called wonderland I
still don't understand why or how I
ended up here but why were you drinking
tea out of his huge butt crack
what are you talking about I wasn't
drinking tea out of his butt crack haha
but I just saw you let's let's just say
that's how we all drink tea in
Wonderland Wonderland is a crazy place a
crazy place
you mean like Gotham City from Batman
yes haha well that's just silly
in the world where I come from we drink
tea out of a cup the only other people
I've ever seen drinking tea out of
someone's butt crack is my brother Sonic
and his boyfriend Bart Levy oh right I'm
sorry I didn't even ask you your names
my name is Sonya they call me the Mad
Hatter
but called I make hats and I'm crazy
Asha my name is maniac the rabbit but
you can just call me maniac cause I'm
crazy as [ __ ] to sounds like everyone in
Wonderland is a little bit crazy you
could say that we're all mad here in
Wonderland
so [ __ ] how did you end up here in
Wonderland in the first place how did I
end up here again oh yeah I was chasing
a white rabbit I was chasing it when I
fell down a hole but now that I think
about it it may not have even been a
rabbit at all but a big muscular man it
couldn't have been a white rabbit this
part of Wonderland is basically a ghetto
but two big muscular man that sounds
like you were talking about Bart Levy
hold the [ __ ] up did you just say Bart
levy
I know Bart levy he's somebody from my
world
well this Bartlett just showed up here
in wonderland 45 minutes ago he's so
rich that he bought all of Wonderland so
now he's basically God that sounds like
Bart levy all right damn just what is he
doing here
you guys look over there there's
something running through the trees well
what are you [ __ ] waiting for
somebody grab him
[Music]
you
I think we lost him damn it that white
rabbit sure is fast I need to take a
breather
maybe go take a [ __ ] come on I think I
saw the white rabbit go this way okay
are you sure you want to go that way
[ __ ] yeah are you sure you want to go
that way
and who the hell are you supposed to be
I'm Tweedledee and he's Tweedledum
actually I'm Tweedledee and he's
Tweedledum we know how to get everywhere
in Wonderland and what you're looking
for isn't over that way are you sure you
don't want to go this way or maybe you
should consider going this way don't
listen to them Sonja they're the
Tweedles they're just trying to mess
with us or maybe you should try going
that way or this way or this way oh my
God
Tweedledum I'm so sorry are you dead did
I kill you I told you my name is
Tweedledee you [ __ ] you son of a [ __ ]
this is the 54th time today you pushed
me into a tree did you know how
embarrassing it is to be pushed into a
tree how many times do I gotta tell you
not to hit me [ __ ] do I go to punish
you the same way I punished you last
night
you you don't have to do that hey since
you know how to get everywhere in
Wonderland can you help us I was
wondering if you might have seen a white
rabbit run by here actually I don't
think it was a rabbit at all but
actually a big muscular man
if you are looking for info under White
Rabbit you're gonna have to talk to
tweedle daddy
tweedle daddy is in the house [ __ ] I
heard that you're looking for that white
rabbit yeah I saw him I also saw a fat
blue boy with a big fat ass chasing
after him a fat glue guy with a big ass
that can only be my brother
Sonic the Hedgehog and if he's chasing
the rabbit then that settles it the
rabbit has to be his boyfriend Bart
Libby I was hoping for the fat one why
are you here
it all makes sense now Bart levy didn't
want me to follow him he wanted Sonic
but the question now is why did Bart
Levy bring Sonic to Wonderland well that
doesn't matter now I'll just ask Sonic
and Bars levy when I see them I'm afraid
that's not going to happen you see while
your brother was chasing after the sexy
man he was attacked and kidnapped by the
evil Red Queen soldiers the Red Queen
who is that the Red Queen is the queen
of Wonderland she rules over all with an
iron fist I'm afraid your brother may
already be dead if not he is locked away
in her dungeon locked away far away from
here deep below the Red Queen's castle
you and your friends should turn back
now so you don't suffer the same fate I
can't just leave my brother if he's in
trouble I had to rescue him if I let
Sonic die my Uncle Chuck would beat my
[ __ ] ass like a drum please tell me
where the Red Queen's castle is right
away
the castle you see can be found over
there but remember you three the perils
you will face will be like none you have
ever faced before
Manek go see Wes onic and Sony ran off -
we're about to leave how the [ __ ] should
I know where they are don't talk to me
[ __ ] I'm trying to play my PSP well
what do you know if it isn't the Oracle
of Delphi
how have you been it's sure been our
while hasn't it
hahaha yep it sure has Queen Aleena
fancy seeing you here in Walmart so what
are you doing here oh you know I'm just
doing a bit of grocery shopping with the
kids what about you are the flowers for
a special event and that bottle of wine
that's some expensive [ __ ] like 800
dollars actually you see I kinda have a
date later tonight a date that's
wonderful Oracle I had no idea you were
seeing anyone what's her name Vernon I I
mean yeah of course she has a name I
mean it's it's not like I ever use it
though you know the cause she's my
[ __ ] [ __ ]
I don't use it because [ __ ] need to
know their place you you know what I
mean
captain squidge what are you still doing
on the phone don't tell me you forgot
about our little arrangement it's
already 3:00 p.m. silly
I'm gonna have to call you back how much
Wilfried now is getting me I'll suck
your balls a lot
you might have been captain of the sea
once captain squid but now it seems you
are just the captain of my ass you
naughty little sea sponge did I say you
could talk without my permission [ __ ]
I I'm sorry I guess I should probably
get going now yeah that would be a good
idea my wife is going to be home in
about ten minutes
[Music]
look there that must be the castle of
the evil [ __ ] it's got to be that's
certainly a castle if I ever saw one and
it's so clean - maybe the queen isn't so
bad after all oh I don't know something
doesn't feel quite right here once this
is all done and we find your brother
maybe we can celebrate with some tea
I'll grill tray this is forbidden
growing for trespassers Alt alt yes I
intend American you command the auto
plant yoga's firmly integral you to get
to safety
I'll take care of this why who is that
what's going on
it's the servants of the Red Queen
they've come to imprison us just like
they did to your brother don't even try
and run yeontae still marry Diana on a
bed of the Royal Guard in training
and my name is Sammy
Oh No
are you okay does it look like he's okay
[ __ ] he used that spear to rip and
they're the clothes from his butt cheeks
I could literally see his ball sack
hanging out your what if oh holy Sh and
wait for Chang Quinta we take in
Vitello's of the with the kingdom Yahweh
by avoid that war teacher yang cares
hold on a second did he say the white
queen so then this place isn't way
please this is some kind of mistake
don't limit that your mother was coming
editor first glossy and not even acousto
in Turkey
ooh in winter appeal to the narrow sir
Knight what in Wonderland are you doing
you're eNOS yo you be blessed token that
you wake up to that the same through
their snaggy novel the ghastly groans
enough nonsense release the poor rabbit
at once there is no need to frighten the
poor thing your way are there yet that
me for a [ __ ] you in tears excuse me for
asking but did you say this is the White
Queen that's right I am the rightful
ruler of Underland at least I should be
but that Red Queen's luck decided to
turn it into her own personal strip
plump oh gosh don't tell me we've been
going the wrong way this whole time how
did this happen
who's the [ __ ] that had the map this is
your fault
no I shouldn't be mad at you guys it's
not your fault it's all that Red Queen I
just wish I knew why she was doing this
what does she want with my brother slots
are just so so God damn evil whoa geez
allow me to tell you what happened on
that fateful day the day the Red Queen
came to be the ruler of Underland
so you're the sister of the Red Queen
the one that rules over Wonderland I was
but that was a long time ago
now I live her here in the White Kingdom
because the Red Queen kicked me out what
happened how did she take over up in
this [ __ ] it all happened because she
did not agree with how her father was my
name of Kingdom he wanted the land to
live in peace at home where all the
people could live as one end of the
quills it was a kingdom where violence
and hatred did not exist but my sister
Mandi did not want that she wanted to be
drooler so she could suck anyone's balls
for free and nobody would be able to
tell her no obviously our dad didn't
approve this instead he just said go
make me a sandwich [ __ ] so she did a
few months later she asked again and he
still said no she just went ahead and
beat him out this time so he ended up
taking the throne and banished off you
disobeyed her
even her own father was taken away and
imprisoned not knowing what else to do
but luckily for you though she keeps all
of her prisoners alive so she can suck
their balls whenever she's bored so my
brother is safe
that's so good to hear but how will we
get there in time we don't even know
where he's locked up at he's just in the
[ __ ] basement [ __ ] hey what do you
see in there hot damn she's only wearing
a bikini I wonder if she will let me
sniff her butt hush I think they're
talking about something you are a
corrupt ruler my daughter why do you
think you can suck people's balls for
free it's just wrong I would never and I
mean never allow this if I were the king
you have gone mad please stop kidnapping
people and sucking their balls for
Heaven's sake
enough from you prisoner return to the
dungeon and wait for me there
you better not have your pants on or I
will be very mad
damn it all I hate that [ __ ] why because
she could nap my great-grandfather's
fare in the dead of night while he was
Sleeting she imprisoned him and sucks
his huge balls I mean he probably likes
it but somebody needs to come home and
make my dinner
don't worry header we will find and
rescue your great-grandfather as well as
onok the Hedgehog
who are you I'm the guy
what's the point it doesn't matter how
much help we get we won't win either way
nothing is a winnable if we join
together we battle as one we plant each
other's strengths and we help cover each
other's weaknesses we can accomplish
anything and we will accomplish
everything first let's go free your
friends and then we'll show this [ __ ]
who's boss are you with me
[Applause]
hurry Bartel be free we don't know when
the gardens will be back I'm so scared I
just farted [ __ ] I'm working shut up
before I make you shut up
by sticking my balls in your mouth
uh-huh
there he is he's alright
bro how did you get here well it's a bit
of a long story but I'll tell you anyway
do you remember that time Bart levy used
his big muscles to pull the entire
universe to smash it into the helicopter
above our house well when he did that he
created a tear in time and space itself
allowing us to enter into this crazy
world of Wonderland
yeah but why are you here Oh Bart levy
thought it would be fun to have kinky
roleplay sex but I got captured because
I couldn't keep up with Bart levy okay
daddy
you would better have your [ __ ] pants
off for already it's time for me to set
your big fat juicy balls as punishment
for disobeying me what the hell is this
Sonic the Hedgehog
how did you get out of your cell who are
all you people and how dare you wear
clothes in my kingdom everybody knows I
have been clothes
when I took the throne sure it's the Red
Queen herself she's here to suck our
balls Bart levy I'm so frightened I
don't want to be locked up again what
will we do
don't worry my Beach just stay behind my
watermelon sized butt cheeks and you
will be safe you can sit this one out
Bartleby
we can't have you doing all the dirty
work if you did everything the rest of
us wouldn't be able to have any fun
leave this [ __ ] with the giant boobies
to me I will give you just one warning
you evil [ __ ] put on some [ __ ]
clothes or else I will [ __ ] how about
you come Nova infect me in the ass
instead okay
while you guys we did it the Red Queen
is finally dead
we saved Wonderland
you three sexy [ __ ] mid wonderland a
great service this day by filling my
daughter I don't know how we could ever
repay you
it's no problem at all your highness we
are just happy to know that wonderland
is finally at peace oh you've got it all
wrong [ __ ] Wonderland isn't at ease in
fact the people of Wonderland are all
rioting right outside these windows it
turns out that the people actually liked
being ruled by my daughter which makes
sense because she was a hot 16 year old
girl who walked around in a bikini and
she would like have sex with literally
any Bobby because of the Queen's death I
calculate that the people of Wonderland
will break down the castle doors in
about an hour
and assassinate me or Sofia Slee I
didn't ask for this this is all your
fault but we are at the end now and I
won't gain anything from blaming you or
whatever I assume you don't want to be
here when I die so I will teleport you
away with my almighty magic so yeah
thanks for [ __ ] me over I guess
you
holy [ __ ]
Manek I'm not playing around go find
your brother and sister it's time to
[ __ ] go
I'm telling you mama I already looked
everywhere it's like they just
disappeared or something what if a
rapist saw how big Sonic's butt was and
kidnapped the two of them then go find
the rapist and tell them to give Sonia
back they can keep Sonic I don't know I
don't give a [ __ ] Manic listen I need to
go find a bathroom if I don't find one
in the next 23 seconds I'm going to poop
my pants
they it looks like we are back in the
real world for really [ __ ] what the
hell gave you that idea
Sonic Sonia there you guys are where did
you run off to
it's a long story my green bean looking
bro I'll tell you all about it later
okay
but right now can you tell me why Bart
levy is naked and standing behind you
like that
voila never mind I see it I can't
believe he's 10 inches deep in your ass
right now and right in the middle of
Walmart - damn my bro you are crazy
haha
[Music]
run free in dive until the sky
here the live cry
in the freedom
[Music]
don't look behind you back